Slapping tariffs on Chinese goods Making us pay while he says it's all good Market numbers taking a dive Consumer confidence barely alive Factories closing down overnight But each week said everything's alright A businessman who went bankrupt four times Now he's running our economy into the brown
Economy and free fall again.
Cherubs and tweets from an egg-o-maniac's band.
Stock market crashing, no sanity or gland.
Just a rich man's game we don't understand.
Hit poor taxes, hit the average show While the billionaires watch their portfolios grow He claims it's America first, but we pay the price When basic economic gets sacrificed Inflation climbing, jobs disappearing fast Building walls on burning bridges, ag would last The average worker feels the squeeze and strain While the White House plays its economic showdave Trade wars aren't easy to win
When you don't know where to begin Shooting yourself in the foot While claiming that it's absolute Economy and people again Tests and tweets from an egomaniac's pen Stock market crashing, go study your twin Just a rich man's gang we don't understand We pay, we pay, we
We pay, we pay, we We pay, we pay for their mistakes